<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Comparator Verifier</title><link>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Comparator Verifier</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Configuration Options</title><link>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/configuration-options/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/configuration-options/</guid><description>Configuration Options # Options can be set using the fluent API. Some options are also available to be set in comparator-verifier.properties which should be on the test classpath, e.g. in src/test/resources. Using the API sets values on a per-test basis, whereas setting a value in the properties file provides a default value for all tests. Values set in via the API will override values in the properties file.
withExamples(T first, T second, T.</description></item><item><title>Explication des avertissements</title><link>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/fr/warnings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/fr/warnings/</guid><description>Explication des avertissements # Cette page présente divers avertissements pouvant survenir lors de la vérification de la validité d&amp;rsquo;une implémentation de Comparator. Chaque avertissement correspond à une propriété contractuelle spécifique qu&amp;rsquo;un comparateur bien implémenté devrait respecter.
🇬🇧 In English 🇵🇱 Po polsku ANTI_SYMMETRY # Un comparateur viole l&amp;rsquo;anti-symétrie s&amp;rsquo;il renvoie des résultats incohérents lorsque l&amp;rsquo;ordre de ses arguments est inversé. Plus précisément, pour tous objets x et y, si compare(x, y) &amp;lt; 0, alors compare(y, x) devrait renvoyer une valeur supérieure à 0.</description></item><item><title>Warnings Explained</title><link>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/warnings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/warnings/</guid><description>Warnings Explained # This page outlines various warnings that may arise when verifying the correctness of a Comparator implementation. Each warning corresponds to a specific contractual property that a well-implemented comparator should uphold. https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/warnings/
🇫🇷 En français 🇵🇱 Po polsku ANTI_SYMMETRY # A comparator violates anti-symmetry if it returns inconsistent results when the order of its arguments is reversed. Specifically, for any objects x and y, if compare(x, y) &amp;lt; 0, then compare(y, x) should return a value greater than 0.</description></item><item><title>Wyjaśnienie ostrzeżeń</title><link>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/pl/warnings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tomregan.github.io/comparatorverifier/docs/pl/warnings/</guid><description>Wyjaśnienie ostrzeżeń # Ta strona przedstawia różne ostrzeżenia, które mogą pojawić się podczas weryfikacji poprawności implementacji Comparatora. Każde ostrzeżenie odpowiada konkretnej właściwości umownej, którą dobrze zaimplementowany comparator powinien spełniać.
🇬🇧 In English 🇫🇷 [En français]/docs/fr/warnings.md) ANTI_SYMMETRY # Comparator narusza zasadę antysymetrii, jeśli zwraca niespójne wyniki, gdy kolejność jego argumentów zostanie odwrócona. Konkretnie, dla dowolnych obiektów x i y, jeśli compare(x, y) &amp;lt; 0, to compare(y, x) powinno zwrócić wartość większą od 0.</description></item></channel></rss>